# **Fallon Easton**

432 Main Road, Tallahassee, FL 65432 f.easton@myemaiL.com (678) 901-2345

Knowledgeable academic librarian with 6+ years' experience managing resources in a thriving university library.

Assertive and motivational Leader with a strong track record for nurturing talent and providing meaningful training opportunities. Excellent collaborative skills and works closely with colleagues to ensure a comprehensive resource selection.

### **Education**

Bachelor of Arts in English Literature

Florida Agricultural And Mechanical University, Tallahassee, Fl
September 2008 -June 2012

Master of Science in Library Science

Florida State University. Tallahassee, Fl September 2012 - June 2014

## **Key Skills**

- Events and service promotion
- Staff management and mentorship
- Cataloging
- Budget management
- Resource acquisition

## **Professional Experience**

#### LIBRARIAN

Florida State University, Tallahassee, FL | September 2014- Present

- Work collaboratively with academic staff to select and purchase a broad range of materials to complement the course curricula
- Adapt the Library resources and environment to meet the needs of a diverse student body and ensure equal access, most recently developing a research suite for students with visual impairments
- Conduct promotional activities and events to encourage students to take advantage of Library resources, resulting in a footfall increase of 21% in 2020
- Source, purchase, and catalog print and digital materials and oversee the departmental budget
- Manage and deploy the library team and conduct performance reviews, target setting, and professional development programs

#### LIBRARY PAGE

Tallahassee Community College, Tallahassee, FL | September 2012 - September 2014

- Organized and shelved books and other printed resources and performed regular inspections of the shelving units
- Assisted with student orientation and provide advice and support with resource location
- Processed book loans and returns and administered fines in line with college policies